abyanadam.id@gmail.com

+62 822-8482-8941

Padang, West Sumatera

Profile Summary

My name is aby, backend developer based in padang, west sumatera, indonesia, with high interest in web development and api development with 3+ years experience in various projects.

During my time in web development, I have worked on projects from various fields such as internal company, micro small business, and startup.

Professional Skill

- Php
 - HTML
- GIT API
- OOP
- Internet
- AJAX • Codelgniter • JavaScript • MySQL

Relevant Skill

- System Analyst • Team work
- Comunication
- Creativ Thinking
- Probelm Solving
- Creativ Visioning

Education

Laravel

Bachelor of Universitas Putra Indonesia "YPTK" Padang

2015-2019

Computer System Or Computer Engineering

Work Experience

CV. Mediatama Web Indonesia

2020

• Web Developer

Konsultan IT & Elektro

2020 - 2022

- Head Of IT Engineering
- Web Programmer

LKP Primadata

2020-2021

• Programming Instructor

PT. Yosa Pertama Solusindo

2020-2022

Web Developer

PT. Suku Maya Teknologi

2021-2023

- Senior Web Developer
- Programming Instructor
- Computer Technician

Interest

Technology

Programming

Creative Design